<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steve Leathers | Realtor</title>
    <description>I&#39;m a Realtor at [Inhabit](http://www.inhabitportland.com), and I live in Portland, Oregon.
</description>
    <link>http://steveleathers.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://steveleathers.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 08:23:01 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 08:23:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title></title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At first, when the Portland bike share system BIKETOWN started rolling out stations all over town, I was dubious. I’m a cyclist, so obviously I like the idea of more bikes on the street, and I’m not particularly offended by BIKETOWN’s loud branding. But I couldn’t really think of a reason to &lt;em&gt;use&lt;/em&gt; BIKETOWN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is, until I found by chain started slipping of my bike just about every time I used it. I took my bike in to be serviced, only to find that I’d need a new chainring, chain, and cassette. It would be about a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m lucky enough to live in a very walkable neighborhood. Basically anything I need is less than a mile from my house, so being bikeless for a week isn’t a big deal. But where BIKETOWN really shines is filling in gaps when I would have rather biked than walked, taken the bus, or driven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://steveleathers.com/images/MississippiCorral.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Biketown Corral on Mississippi Avenue in North Portland&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It adds a whole new layer of options for me. Where I would have taken a car to go, or &lt;em&gt;maybe&lt;/em&gt; taken the bus (if I were along a 4 or 44 line), I can now hop on a bike without having to wait, get some exercise, and not have to pay quite as much as I would have otherwise. It’s also fun to think of opportunities to get friends and family who are visiting from out of town on bikes so they can experience the city like I usually do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I found the whole system amazingly intuitive to figure out, and the bike was surprisingly comfortable to ride around. It’s worth noting that these bikes are &lt;em&gt;heavy&lt;/em&gt;, though. I think it’s safe to say that my 4 mile ride from the Boise neighborhood to Industrial SE Portland would normally take me 15-20 minutes, and with BIKETOWN it took about 25.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://steveleathers.com/images/BiketownTrip.png&quot; alt=&quot;My first BIKETOWN trip&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But maybe that’s a good thing! An extra 5 minutes isn’t all that much for a quick trip like this. Sometimes it’s nice to go slow. You get a chance to see things that you normally wouldn’t, and there’s no question that going slow is generally much safer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the Inhabit office on SE Division, we’re close to the Southeastern service area of BIKETOWN, but luckily we’re in between two large corrals of bikes at SE 30th and SE 34th. If you’re in the neighborhood and want to give BIKETOWN a shot and see what it’s all about, give me a call or send me an email. Your first ride’s on me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://steveleathers.com/images/DivisionCorral.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Biketown Corral on Division Street in Southeast Portland&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 08:23:01 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://steveleathers.com/2016/09/08/2016-07-27-go-by-bike.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://steveleathers.com/2016/09/08/2016-07-27-go-by-bike.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
