<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Steve Leathers | Portland, Oregon Realtor | steveleathers.com</title>
    <description>I&#39;m a Realtor at [Inhabit](http://www.inhabitportland.com), and I live in Portland, Oregon.
</description>
    <link>http://steveleathers.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://steveleathers.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 09:43:16 -0700</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 09:43:16 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Go By Bike(town)</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;At first, when BIKETOWN started rolling out stations all over town, I was dubious. I like the idea of more bikes on the street, and I’m not particularly offended by BIKETOWN’s loud branding. But I couldn’t really think of a reason to &lt;em&gt;use&lt;/em&gt; BIKETOWN.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That is, until I found by chain started slipping of my bike just about every time I used it. I took my bike in to be serviced, only to find that I’d need a new chainring, chain, and cassette. It would be about a week.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’m lucky enough to live in a very walkable neighborhood. Basically anything I need is less than a mile from my house, so being bikeless for a week isn’t a big deal. But where BIKETOWN really shines is filling in gaps when I would have rather biked than walked, taken the bus, or driven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It adds a whole new layer of options for me. Where I would have taken a car to go, or &lt;em&gt;maybe&lt;/em&gt; taken the bus (if I were along a 4 or 44 line), I can now hop on a bike without having to wait, get some exercise, and not have to pay quite as much as I would have otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jul 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://steveleathers.com/2016/07/27/go-by-bike.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://steveleathers.com/2016/07/27/go-by-bike.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
